[Late one night]
[An abandoned warehouse]
(DOHOON) Guys!
[KYUNGMIN) Guys!
(HANJIN) Guys! Can you hear me?
Oh no...
Oh no
Ah...
I don't think I can do this
Seriously, right now
it feels like there's someone behind me
I guess everyone's starting separately
I'm the worst at doing things on my own
I don't want to scream
Oh no
I hope I'll do well
My goal is to survive until the end
and that's it
This is crazy
Get it together
I just need to get it together
I'll survive no matter what
[A suspicious being is searching for TWS]
[Get caught]
(YOUNGJAE) I'll hang in there for dear life
[or survive till the end]
He's here
[Never-ending game in the dark]
It's over for me
I'm so scared
(JIHOON) Hold up
(JIHOON) Something's wrong
(JIHOON) This isn't right!
It's so real...
We're in trouble
Wow...
Seriously, what is this?
Oh my god
Hold up
Seriously, KYUNGMIN
Guys...
(KYUNGMIN) Guys!
I'm really bad at stuff like this
I can't see in front of me
Wow
Can they do this?
Why did they put me here?
Seriously, what is this?
What am I supposed to do?
[DOHOON shrieking]
[Some kind of head]
This is crazy
What is this?
It's so scary... What is this?
I don't think I can do this
Wait
so are we supposed to hide? No?
I'm really scared
Wait, I'm not scared
This is just a factory, nothing to it
That's right
But this spot is a bit scary
[HANJIN] [YOUNGJAE] [KYUNGMIN]
[JIHOON] [SHINYU] [DOHOON]
[Phone notification]
(JIHOON) Whoa, why's this so loud?
(KYUNGMIN) Something just arrived
(HANJIN) I just got a text
(DOHOON) Oh no...
From now on, find hidden keys
in anything that can move
If the seeker catches you
you can use a key to get free or
you can free another member
You can escape once with one key
Do I have to search
for a key here?
I don't see anything
What does a key look like?
What's 'something that moves'?
Let's give this a shot... Let's go
I don't see anything
We're starting, right?
Look for the keys
in something that moves
Feels like...
The keys would be hidden here
[TWS each go searching for the keys]
[Special effects sound]
What is that?
It made me jump...
Nah, I'm not scared
I'm not scared or anything
I'm just a little worried
Well...
The keys
[Hears something nearby]
It was probably the director
I'm sorry
I said I wasn't scared
I don't think there're any keys here
♪ Keys, keys ♪
♪ Where are you ♪
[HANJIN]
Guys!
(HANJIN) Can you hear me?
(HANJIN) Guys?
(HANJIN) KYUNGMIN!
[DOHOON→]
Guys!
(KYUNGMIN) DOHOON!
Hey!
[KYUNGMIN] [DOHOON]
[Meets KYUNGMIN as soon as he steps outside]
Did you come out from over there?
(KYUNGMIN) Yeah!
(DOHOON) Hey, but
can we even find these keys?
We have to
I'm so scared of the seeker
But right now
the seeker is definitely not out there
I can hear footsteps
The seeker isn't here now
and the keys are definitely in these boxes
I don't see any keys at all
[DOHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
[They separate to look for the keys]
Should I climb up here?
What's this?
(DOHOON) This is totally crazy
(DOHOON) Wow, it's so scary up here
It's so scary I can't do this
But
I'll try and do this thing
and not be scared this time
[HANJIN's voice calls from afar]
[← HANJIN] [DOHOON →]
[DOHOON didn't hear him]
There aren't any keys
I think
I shouldn't be here
Usually I totally can't go to places
like this on my own
[DOHOON]
I think I'm pretty awesome
[JIHOON]
I have no idea
what this place is
How are we supposed to find the keys?
The seeker's probably not out yet
[JIHOON spots something]
It says to push
(JIHOON) It says 'Please push'
I don't think I should push this
Should I try?
Let me go push it
What's that?
[A horrifying scream rings out]
[And someone comes towards JIHOON]
Who's that?
(JIHOON) I pressed something
(YOUNGJAE) Haven't we started yet?
We've started, right?
I don't know
Why did it say 'push'?
We've started, right?
[He tries pushing it again]
I fell for it!
[It has nothing to do with the seeker]
[YOUNGJAE] [JIHOON]
How come you're moving around so well?
I don't think the seeker's here yet
[YOUNGJAE] [JIHOON]
[YOUNGJAE]
[SHINYU] [YOUNGJAE]
[SHINYU still hasn't left the starting point]
Seriously
I need to get a hold of myself
I just need to get a hold of myself
There's nothing to be scared of
[Footsteps coming closer]
It's one of the members!
[Footsteps belong to YOUNGJAE]
[← SHINYU] [YOUNGJAE →]
Woah!
Oh...
Woah...
[Going around and finally finding each other]
[YOUNGJAE leaves SHINYU and hides first]
Do I have to hide too?
(YOUNGJAE) This looks like a good spot
[YOUNGJAE finds a safe place to hide]
[SHINYU]
[SHINYU goes deeper looking for a hiding spot]
Should I hide?
I'm going to hide here
(SHINYU) I'm not going to fit
Oh no!
This looks good
(SHINYU) I can fit in here
(SHINYU) This spot is amazing
I'm going to listen for anything out there
and then I'll move
[SHINYU's hidden behind a wall]
(SHINYU) Right now...
(SHINYU) I'm aiming to hide till the end
(SHINYU) I won't be captured
[Phone alert]
It's a hint for the keys!
[Hint for the keys]
[SHINYU checks the hint too]
I won't need keys
in the first place
if I don't get caught and stay hidden
Yeah, this is the way to go
Let's wait it out
[SHINYU's sigh]
(SHINYU) This is really scary
(SHINYU) I need to put my phone
on silent mode
(SHINYU) How do I silence it?
(SHINYU) Vibrate
(SHINYU) Okay
I've put it in vibrate mode
I'm so clever
like this...
I have to be clever like this
[Phone vibrates]
(YOUNGJAE) (Phone alert) I'm going to
put this on silent mode
Shouldn't I just stay over here like this?
Then we just win
[HANJIN]
Stay positive
Think positive thoughts, HANJIN
If I get caught... well...
I'll just...
Oh!
[← Golf clubs]
What if I keep this with me?
I'll just take this along just in case
The keys...
Should I open this?
[HANJIN opens the fridge]
Ah!
Isn't this that thing?
[Finds a thrown-out cactus doll]
Ah! Ah!
This is cute!
[The cactus starts singing]
I'll use this to distract the seeker
Is it too noisy?
Why did it turn off automatically?
Oh my gosh!
Why do you look so cute?
[Ran into a street sweeper]
I found it!
[HANJIN finds the first key in the sweeper]
HANJIN, did you find the car keys?
You made me jump!
(HANJIN) I thought you were the seeker
[Phone alert]
[The next hint arrives]
[Hint to the keys]
Where is this?
Where's this place?
[HANJIN] [KYUNGMIN]
Where are the others?
I don't know
I found it
[JIHOON finds the second key in the manual forklift]
I found a key
I found it
'Moving things'
wasn't what I had in mind
It was stuff like forklifts
I will never get caught
so I'll use this for the other members
I just need to find a good place to hide
I need to figure out where I am
I've got it. I'm going to set up
my hiding place
It's going to look like there's nothing there
[Just then, someone goes toward JIHOON]
If I keep calm, I'll be fine
[Feels someone's presence]
Wow!
DOHOON, did you find anything?
Did you see the hint?
Yeah, did you find anything?
-I didn't find anything
-I found one
-What?
-A key!
I think since I found a key
the game's going to start
I have to find a hiding place
(DOHOON) This place is seriously scary
(DOHOON) Can I go there?
[DOHOON enters the machinery room]
I'm so scared!
Where am I supposed to go?
(YOUNGJAE) I can hear DOHOON's voice
(YOUNGJAE) It's DOHOON. DOHOON!
(YOUNGJAE) Feels like DOHOON
[YOUNGJAE →]
(YOUNGJAE) Nobody's going to find me here
[DOHOON enters the generator room in the machine room]
[DOHOON gets a fright]
(?) DOHOON
What?
-(DOHOON) Who is that?
-(SHINYU) It's me Junghwan
You gave me a fright! Why're you hiding?
Do we have to keep moving?
I don't know what we're supposed to do
(DOHOON) We need to keep moving!
We do?
(DOHOON) We need to move around
and find the keys
(DOHOON) You shouldn't hide!
We need to find the keys
I don't think the seeker's here yet
Do they alert us when the seeker's out?
I think so!
(SHINYU) You're great at moving around
The seeker's not around
-(DOHOON) It's not here
-(SHINYU) Hey, DOHOON
[SHINYU just got a big fright from something]
I just heard a mace...
It sounded like a mace
[SHINYU manages to come out thanks to DOHOON]
[DOHOON] [After leaving SHINYU, he goes to another room]
Is this a suitcase?
I'm going to open this
What!
What's this?
(HANJIN) Why?
Did you find it?
[DOHOON finds the third key in the suitcase]
Oh!
(DOHOON) I found it!
(DOHOON) This is amazing
[Phone alert]
[Got a text]
[Hint for the keys]
[KYUNGMIN] [Sees the hint and starts moving]
I think it's the third one
This spot is important for the third one
[← KYUNGMIN] [← HANJIN]
[HANJIN is right behind KYUNGMIN]
[↑ HANJIN] [↑ KYUNGMIN]
Red...
[Hint for a key] [HANJIN finds the frame in the hint]
[But he can't find any keys]
-Did you find the key?
-No
But this is the place
[This place is full of fog]
[At that moment]
Something's written here
Look for a movable wooden box
and move it within the frame
and shine the flashlight on top of the box
[and you will find the key]
We have to look for a movable wooden box
(HANJIN) A movable box?
[They start searching the boxes nearby]
Something movable...
HANJIN, I think this one can move
-That's not it
-Huh?
-It said a wooden box
-But this is wood
That's wood? Isn't it cardboard?
-It's not
-Maybe this isn't it
Isn't it this? A wooden box!
-This one moves
-Yeah! Let's go
[Found two movable wooden boxes]
(KYUNGMIN) Let's go
KYUNGMIN, be careful
Let's put one in first
Here's the flashlight
You don't need to bring that
[KYUNGMIN shines the light on top of the box]
It says it's empty
(HANJIN) Really? Then it's this one
[They check the other box]
- This one is also empty
- Empty?
-KYUNGMIN!
-JIHOON! Come over here
-JIHOON!
-(JIHOON) Yeah?
-There's a box here
-(JIHOON) Yeah
Bring all of those boxes
-Why?
-Can you bring that one over?
-Which box?
-This one says 'empty'
[Another similar-looking box nearby]
I think it's this one
This one's a little heavy
[The three of them carefully move the box]
I'm going to check now
[Checks the password]
[DOHOON who was passing by also joins in]
What's going on?
We can get a key if we do this
These guys were doing it
The four of us shouldn't be together
I shouldn't be here right now
While the other members
are doing the mission
I'll go and check out our location
854!
[The lock opens]
Be careful
What's this?
[The box is filled with packing peanuts]
We need to find the key in here
I found it
[KYUNGMIN screams]
[DOHOON jumps and drops the key]
You found it
Now I'm the seeker
They're insane
I knew they'd do that
[Hide-and-seek begins]
Are you okay?
[KYUNGMIN is lying down in shock]
What's wrong?
[The three guys run away from the seeker]
Ready or not
here I come
[←DOHOON]
Oh no, what do I do?
I'm not ready yet
Ready or not
here I come DOHOON
Why am I so scared right now
[DOHOON goes into the corner of the warehouse]
[Hides inside the transparent plastic]
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN]
HANJIN, there's a hole here
It's okay
Are you in?
[← HANJIN and KYUNGMIN] [Hiding in the table]
[SHINYU]
(SHINYU) It's too tight
[Phone alert]
[Hide-and-seek starts now]
Play time is 4,444 seconds
If you get caught by the seeker
you go to prison
The survival rate is very important
in this game
If the survival rate is over 50%
then 42 (SAI) will receive presents
so do your best and get a high survival rate
We need to give 42 (SAI) presents
[↑ JIHOON]
[Hidden behind the stacked boxes]
[DOHOON] [HANJIN and KYUNGMIN]
[SHINYU] [JIHOON]
[YOUNGJAE]
Ready or not
here I come
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓]
(KYUNGMIN) I think we hid pretty well
(HANJIN) Yeah
KYUNGMIN, I was so scared earlier
I thought you were hurt or something
I just collapsed there
Shhh
[The seeker's footsteps]
Please don't come! I'm going to faint
[← DOHOON] [HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓]
Oh no
Please
[← DOHOON] [HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓]
[The seeker goes towards the members]
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓][SEEKER↓] [DOHOON↓]
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓][SEEKER↓] [←DOHOON]
[The seeker's footsteps fade]
[←DOHOON] [HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓]
(HANJIN) Wow, the seeker's gone
(HANJIN) The seeker's gone
[The seeker] [JIHOON]
[The seeker and JIHOON are far apart]
(JIHOON) My hair color is way too bright
I want to go the place I set up earlier
but I don't know if I'll make it
It's also close to the prison
[Can hear someone appearing]
[JIHOON→]
[SHINYU→]
Can you see how I'm sweating?
(SHINYU) Guys, I'm going crazy over here
(SHINYU) I can't do this anymore
(Seeker)
[← DOHOON] [HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓]
(KYUNGMIN) Wait, hold on
(KYUNGMIN) I don't know if you can see
the light from outside
Cover up the light
Okay
[←DOHOON] [HANJIN and KYUNGMIN↓]
[The seeker's footsteps]
Shhh
[Found you, DOHOON!]
[DOHOON's scream]
Please stop! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Don't take me!
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN laugh]
(DOHOON) Okay, fine! I'm going
DOHOON... I just heard him scream
This is my opportunity
I need to escape
DOHOON just screamed
He just got caught, this is crazy
Let's go now
I need to escape
That's it
[YOUNGJAE] [JIHOON]
Where is it?
I found it
[JIHOON hides in the location he set up
before the game started]
[YOUNGJAE] [JIHOON]
I did it!
[JIHOON  →] [SHINYU goes past JIHOON]
I had a hideout spot checked out earlier
A spot where nobody can find me
Let's hide
I'll hide here
This is the best hiding spot
[Goes in the generator room in the machine room]
[YOUNGJAE] [SHINYU]
Wow, this is so scary
I'm sorry 42, I didn't hide very well
[SHINYU] [DOHOON] [YOUNGJAE] [HANJIN]
[JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
[YOUNGJAE] [SHINYU] [←YOUNGJAE]
(YOUNGJAE) I think this is a good hiding spot
I wonder if the other members are okay